spoofbox.com 2018-08-08

# Privacy policy

##### Our privacy policy

##### **About**

spoofbox.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. We take your privacy seriously. You can learn more about our Privacy Policy below. By visiting spoofbox.com.com, using our mobile app or using our services, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

##### **What does this privacy policy cover?**

This policy covers how spoofbox.com treats personal information that spoofbox.com collects and receives. This includes information related to your past use of spoofbox.com products and services and information about you that is personally identifiable-such as your name, address, email address, or phone number. This Privacy Policy, however, does not apply to the practices of companies that are not affiliated with spoofbox.com. 

##### **What information do we collect and how do we use it?**

spoofbox.com collects personal information when you register for spoofbox.com services or use spoofbox.com features and products. When you register, we ask for personal information, including but not limited to your name, email address, payment information and zip code. Once you register with spoofbox.com and sign into our services, you are not anonymous to us. spoofbox.com also collects information about your transactions with us, including information about your use of our services. We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address and spoofbox.com cookie information. spoofbox.com uses the information for the following purposes, among others: to fulfil your requests for products and services, to improve our services, and to contact you. 

##### **Sharing and/or disclosing information**

Information about our customers is an important part of our business. We share customer information only as described below. spoofbox.com may disclose customers' personal information in the following situations: We may respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal requirements, or seek to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We believe it is necessary to disclose such information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations of spoofbox.com's Terms of Service. 

If spoofbox.com is acquired by or merged with another company, the terms of this Privacy Policy shall continue to apply. In this event, spoofbox.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. spoofbox.com also reserves the right to display targeted advertisements based on personal information. 

##### **spoofbox.com cookies**

spoofbox.com may set and access spoofbox.com cookies on your computer. We also let other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Those cookies are independent of spoofbox.com and are subject to the privacy policies of the company placing the cookie, not to this policy. 

When you visit our website, we, like most websites, send one or more cookies—small anonymous identifiers—to your computer that uniquely identify you to our servers. While we do use cookies for security and fraud investigation purposes, our primary purpose is to enhance your user experience by understanding and remembering your preferences, and by general tracking of our user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or to notify you when a cookie is sent. Please be aware that this website may not have full functionality if your browser refuses cookies. We utilize the following types of cookies: 

Strictly Necessary Cookies: These cookies are strictly necessary to provide services that you have requested on our website. 

Functional Cookies: These cookies support and facilitate your use of our website by enabling enhanced and personalized features. 

Performance Cookies: These cookies collect information that we utilize to support the measurement of this website. 

Targeting Cookies: These cookies are used by social sharing services (such as Facebook), and also by various third parties to deliver messaging that may be of value or interest to you. We do not have access to read or write such third-party cookies, nor do we directly control the manner in which they may be used. 

##### **Your right to edit and delete your information**

You can contact spoofbox.com to edit or delete your spoofbox.com personal information at any time if you have terminated your business relationship with us. spoofbox.com does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell products for purchase by adults, although they may be used by children. If you are under 18, you may use the spoofbox.com website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

##### **Confidentiality and security**

spoofbox.com limits internal access to your personal information to employees who we reasonably believe require this information in order to do their jobs or to provide products and services to you. 

##### **Conclusion**

spoofbox.com may update this policy at any time. We will notify you about any substantive changes in the way we treat your personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address you specified in your spoofbox.com account application or by placing a notice in a prominent place on our web site. If you have further questions or suggestions regarding spoofbox.com's Privacy Policy, you can contact us.
